Subscribe to the bankbajar.com
channel and press the bell button
to watch the video first Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
bankbajar.com Friends, if you have an
account in IDFC Bank, then watch this video
carefully In this video, we will
tell you important information related to it
Friends, today we will tell you
how you can transfer any funds from your ICICI Bank account
So let's start the video
For this, you
should activate the mobile application on your mobile If
you have not activated this application yet, then
we have given the link in the description You
can activate the mobile application
and after activating it, log in You
will subscribe
You have to click on this button And see,
an option of add is coming here After that,
your one time transfer approved 1000 is coming below
So you will go to add from here and
set all your details
See, here we will enter the account number
After that, you have to enter the account
number Then you have to
write the account holder's name here And after that, you have to
enter the IFSC code here
And after that, whatever amount you
want to transfer, you have to print it here,
after that you
will see an ad here, you will click on the proceed button,
and your next button will open, it will
show you whatever name you have
entered, the account number you have entered,
all the details will be
shown there and if all the details are correct
then you will save this detail by clicking on the submit button there,
as soon as
you submit, your PIMS will open
where it will ask you for OTP
and you will see that you have received the TV here
and we will enter this OTP here,
after entering the OTP, our
PIMS details have been successfully saved here,
now here we have to enter the amount,
whatever amount we want to transfer, we will
click next here, whatever amount we want to transfer,
after that we will see below, we can create IM, we can
appoint, we can do RTGS,
if the amount is more than two lakh rupees then
we do RTGS
and if it is less than that then we  If you do Inactive and
IMPS then in this way you
want to transfer, then you can take Next9 and IMPS
or if you
want to transfer more amount then you
can transfer through RTGS, so let's
submit here and after that the
success button is coming from below, then you will
click on the process button here and it is
asking for your confirmation here, all the
details are being filled here and after that you will
confirm here and after
pronouncing your mobile, you will
print the PIN, then your time dictionary has been
fried properly but
we have received its message and it has been
successfully transferred,
so friends this was a simple process of
transferring funds by adding your net pack, in this
you can transfer maximum amount,
now we tell you that if you have to
transfer less than 10 years then
you do not have to enter anyone's details, you will
go directly to the account and
enter their details once and
press it, then the money will be
transferred to it, here you do not have to add  There is
no need for this
but its limit is only Rs.10000
and you can transfer only less than Rs.10,000 on it. If
you want to transfer more than Rs.10,000
then you will have to do this transaction
in RTGS mode and that too by doing PAT. So
see, from here we have tapped and
submitted, so this connection has been done
successfully. So friends, this was the
IMP ad tips process. If you liked this video then
like this video and
subscribe to this channel and friends,
if you also
need any information related to ICICI Bank account or you are facing any
problem in fund transfer
then you can comment us or you
can also mail us on our mail ID.
We have given the mail ID in the description. So
friends, that's all for today. We will
meet you soon with a new video. Thank you
friends.